Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President for Research (University of Michigan), Records, 1950-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Charles G. Overberger, 1950-1982
  - Topical Files
    - 1975-1983
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (CRED), 1979-80 (Box 57)
      - Economics, Department of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Education, American Council on, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Education, School of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - EDUCOM (Interuniversity Communications Council, Inc.), 1980 (Box 57)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory, 1979-1980 (Box 57)
      - Electron Microscopy Laboratory Financial Reports, 1979-80 (Box 57)
      - Energy Research Advisory Committee, Office of, 1979-80 (Box 57)
      - Energy Research, Office of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Engineering, College of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - English, Department of, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1980 (Box 57)
      - Environmental Programs, Council for, 1975-1982 (Box 58)
      - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Epidemiology, Department of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Equipment Needs, 1980 (Box 58)
      - E General (Box 58)
      - Faculty, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Faculty Achievements, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Financial Aid, Office of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Flint Campus, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Food and Drug Administration, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Football Lunches, 1979-80 (Box 58)
      - Ford Henry, Hospital, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
      - F General, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Gelman Sciences, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
      - Gender Research, 1980 (Box 58)
      - General Tire and Rubber Company, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Geology and Mineralogy, Department of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Gerontology, Institute of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Governmental Relations, Council on, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Graduate School, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center, 1980 (Box 58)
      - G General, 1977-1980 (Box 58)
      - Hazardous Waste Research Center, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Health Effects Institute, 1981 (Box 58)
      - Health Sciences, Division of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Higher Education, Center for the Study of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Highway Safety Research Institute, 1980-81 (Box 58)
      - Human Genetics, Department of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Hybridoma Facility, 1981 (Box 58)
      - ICI Americas, Inc., 1981 (Box 58)
      - Indirect Costs, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Industrial Development Division (IST), 1980 (Box 58)
      - Industry/University Relations, 1961-1980 (Box 58)
      - Inquiries and Miscellaneous Questions, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Institutional Cooperation, Committee on (CIC), 1980 (Box 58)
      - Intermedia Transport Research Center (proposal), 1980 (Box 58)
      - Internal Medicine, Department of, 1980 (Box 58)
      - International Business Machines, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
      - International Fisheries and Aquaculture Development, Consortium for, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Invitation, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Irwin International Industries, Inc., 1980 (Box 58)
      - I General, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation, 1980-1982 (Box 58)
      - Labor, Department of, 1980-81 (Box 58)
      - Laboratory Animal Medicine, Unit For
        - Committee on Use and Care of Animals, 1980 (Box 58)
        - Unit, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Lickert, Rensis Lickert Associates, 1980 (Box 58)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 1979-80 (Box 58)
      - MacArthur Foundation (John and Catherine), 1980 (Box 59)
      - Macromolecular Research Center, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Management and Budget, Office of (Federal), 1980 (Box 59)
      - Material and Metallurgical Engineering, Department of, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Mathematics, Department of, 1980 (Box 59)
      - McGraw Hill Observatory, 1979-1982 (Box 59)
      - Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Distinguished Faculty Lectureship in Biomedical Research, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Medical Science Research Building, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Medicinal Chemistry, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Mental Health Research Institute, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Mental Retardation, Institute for Study of, 1980 (Box 59)
      - MERIT (Michigan Educational Resources and Information Triad)
        - General, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Board of Directors, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Michigan Sea Grant
        - External Advisory Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 59)
        - Policy Committee, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Program, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Site Visit, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Michigan, State of
        - Economic Development, 1980-81 (Box 59)
        - Genetic Engineering, Governor's Commission on, 1981 (Box 59)
        - Hazardous Waste Management Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
        - Industrial Development, Discussion Paper for Governor, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Management and Budget, Department of, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Research Development Authority, 1980 (Box 59)
        - Senate Bills (pending), 1980 (Box 59)
      - Michigan Technology Council, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Michigan Transportation Research Program
        - General
          - 1980-81 (Box 59)
          - 1982 (Box 59)
        - Advisory Committee, 1979-1982; 2 folders (Box 59)
        - Cooperative Automobile Research Program, 1979-1982 (Box 59)
        - Program 384246 (Box 59)
        - Program 384336 (Box 59)
      - Microbiology and Immunology, Department of, 1980 (Box 59)
      - Microelectronic Research Center, 1981 (Box 60)
      - Middle English Dictionary, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Midwest Association of Scientists and Engineers, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
      - M General, 1978-1980 (Box 60)
      - National Academy of Sciences, 1980 (Box 60)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1981 (Box 60)
      - National Commission on Research, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
      - National Council of University Research Administrators, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977-1982 (Box 60)
      - National Institute of Education, 1980 (Box 60)
      - National Institute of Health
        - General, 1980 (Box 60)
        - BRSG Program (Biomedical Research Support Grant), 1980; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - National Institute of Mental Health Controversy, 1980-81 (Box 60)
      - National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, 1980 (Box 60)
      - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration Regional Facility, 1980-81 (Box 60)
      - National Research Service Award Act, 1980 (Box 60)
      - National Science Board, 1977 (Box 60)
      - National Science Foundation
        - General, 1979-80 (Box 60)
        - Budget, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
        - Study on University/Industry Research Interactions, 1981 (Box 60)
      - Natural Resources, School of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Department of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Naval Research, Office of, 1981 (Box 60)
      - Neurology, Department of, 1980-1982 (Box 60)
      - Neurosurgical Head Protection Program, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Nuclear Engineering, Department of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1979-80 (Box 60)
      - Nursing, School of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Nutritional Research Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 60)
      - N General, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health, Department of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Ophthalmology, Department of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - O General (Box 60)
      - Patents
        - General, 1980 (Box 60)
        - Federal, 1980
          - Voorhees, Dr. J.J., 1980-81 (Box 60)
      - Payroll Office, 1979-80 (Box 60)
      - Personnel, Department of, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Pharmacology, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Phoenix Project (Michigan Memorial)
        - General, 1980 (Box 60)
        - Reactor Emergency Plan, 1980 (Box 60)
        - Reactor Operations, 1980 (Box 60)
      - Physical Education, Department of, 1979-80 (Box 61)
      - Physics, Department of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Physiology, Department of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Political and Social Research, Inter-University Consortium for, 1979-80 (Box 61)
      - Population Studies, Center for, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Position Emission Tomography, 1980 (Box 61)
      - President-University of Michigan
        - General, 1980 (Box 61)
        - Inquiries, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Priority Fund, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Proctor and Gamble, 1980-1982 (Box 61)
      - Proposal and Award Activity (Report to Deans and Directors), 1980 (Box 61)
      - Psychiatric Hospitals, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Psychiatry, Department of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Psychology, Department of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Public Health, School of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Radiation Control Service, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Radiation Policy Committee, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Recommendations, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Regents
        - Communications, 1980 (Box 61)
        - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Religious Studies Program, 1979-1981 (Box 61)
      - Renovations-Buildings, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research, General, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research Development Administration, Division of (DRDA)
        - General, 1980 (Box 61)
        - Review Committee, 1979-80 (Box 61)
      - Research Figures-University of Michigan, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research Incentives, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research, National Conference on the Advancement of, 1980-1982 (Box 61)
      - Research News, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research Objectives, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Research, Volume of, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Science and Technology, Institute of, 1980 (Box 62)
      - SCRIPT (Stanford Computerized Research Information Profile Technique), 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Sea Grant Association, 1975-1981 (Box 62)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1980 (Box 62)
      - Service Awards, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Signature Authorization, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Simpson Memorial Institute, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Social Research Institute for, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Social Work, School of, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Solar Energy, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Space Inventory, 1974-1980 (Box 62)
      - Spencer Foundation Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Sports Medicine Program, 1980 (Box 62)
      - State and Community Relations, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
      - State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, National Association of, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Statistical Research Laboratory, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Students
        - General, 1980 (Box 62)
        - Minority, 1979-1981 (Box 62)
      - S General, 1978-1980 (Box 62)
      - Technological Assessment, Office of, 1979-1982 (Box 62)
      - Technology Research Center, 1981 (Box 62)
      - Technology Transfer Center, 1981 (Box 62)
      - Texas Instruments Foundation's Founder's Prize, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Tisch Proposal D, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Transportation, U.S. Department of
        - General, 1977-1980 (Box 62)
        - Meeting with Secretary of, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Travel, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Tropical Studies, Organization for, 1978-1982 (Box 62)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1980 (Box 62)
      - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1981 (Box 62)
      - University Research Association
        - General, 1980-81 (Box 62)
        - Council of Presidents, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Universities Space Research Association, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
      - Urban Regional Planning, 1980 (Box 62)
      - U General, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Values and Science, Collegiate Institute for, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Veteran's Administration (VA Hospital), 1980-1982 (Box 62)
      - Vice-President
        - Academic Affairs, 1980 (Box 62)
        - Chief Financial Officer, 1980 (Box 62)
        - Development and University Relations (Box 62)
        - Research
          - General, 1980 (Box 62)
          - Arts and Humanities Advisor, 1980 (Box 62)
          - Assistant, 1980 (Box 62)
          - Federal Relations, 1980 (Box 62)
          - 3 D Letters, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Warner Lambert, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Water Resources Program, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
      - Water Resources, University Council on, 1980 (Box 62)
      - Water Science Review Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
      - Waterman, Alan T., Award, 1979-1981 (Box 62)
      - Wilson, Joseph C., Award, 1979-1981 (Box 62)
      - Wolf Prize, 1979-80 (Box 62)
      - Zoology, Museum of, 1980 (Box 62)
    - 1976-1984
      (primarily 1980-1981)
      - Administrative Systems, Office of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Aerospace Engineering, Department of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Affirmative Action, 1977-1981 (Box 63)
      - Alumnae Athena Award, 1978-1981 (Box 63)
      - American Universities, Association of (AAU), 1981 (Box 63)
      - Anatomy and Cell Biology, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Anthropology, Department of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Anthropology, Museum of, 1980 (Box 63)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Argonne National Laboratory, 1979-1981
        - Award to Dr. Alvin Jensen, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
        - Faculty Research Leave Program, 1979-1981 (Box 63)
      - Argonne Universities, 1979-1981
        - Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 63)
        - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 63)
        - Member Universities, 1979-1981 (Box 63)
      - Art, Museum of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Art, School of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Arthritis Division, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Astronomy, Department of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science, Department of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Atmospheric Research, National Center for, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Atmospheric Research, University Corporation for
        - Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 63)
        - Member's Representatives, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
        - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Automotive Transportation, Office for the Study of, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Awards, Nominations for Misc., 1979-1981 (Box 63)
      - A General, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Bifad and Title XII, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Biological Chemistry, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Biological Safety Officer, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Biological Sciences, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Biomedical Research Council
        - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 63)
        - Membership, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
      - Biophysics Research Division-IST, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Botanical Gardens, 1981 (Box 63)
      - Budget, 1981; 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Budget, Federal, 1978 (Box 64)
      - Bush, Vannevar, Award, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Business Administration, School of, 1981 (Box 64)
      - B General, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Capital Campaign, UM, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Chemistry, Department of, 1981 (Box 64)
      - China, People's Republic of, 1980 (Box 64)
      - CIPRNET/UNIX, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Circular A21; Effort Reporting (and revision 1988), 1981 (Box 64)
      - Classified Research, 1979-1981 (Box 64)
      - Cohan, Bruce E., Professor, 1977-1981 (Box 64)
      - Communication, Department of, 1980-1981 (Box 64)
      - Computer and Communication Sciences, Department of, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Computer and Image Processing Research Network, 1981 (Box 64)
      - Computer Center (ISR Batch Station)
        - 1981 (Box 64)
        - 1982 (Box 64)
      - Computer Center, UM NET
        - 1980-1981 (Box 64)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 64)
      - Computer Policy and Utilization, University Committee on
        - General
          - 1968-1969 (Box 64)
          - 1969-1970 (Box 64)
          - 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 64)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 64)
          - 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 64)
          - 1974-1979 (Box 64)
          - 1980 (Box 64)
            [see also Charles G. Overberger Series Topical file, 1975-1983 (box 56)]
          - 1981 (Box 65)
          - 1982 (Box 65)
          - 1983 (Box 65)
        - Review
          - 1981 (Box 65)
          - 1982 (Box 65)
          - 1983 (Box 65)
      - Computing Center
        - 1981 (Box 65)
        - Advisory Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 65)
        - Executive Committee, 1977-1984 (Box 65)
        - MTS License agreements, 1981 (Box 65)
        - MAGI License agreements, 1981 (Box 65)
        - Microcomputer policy, subcommittee on progress report of the, 1984 (Box 65)
        - Phototypesetter for, 1983-1984 (Box 65)
        - Special account for carryovers (computer use), 1981 (Box 66)
        - Word processing, 1980 (Box 66)
      - Conflict of Interest Committee, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Congratulation Correspondence (KUDOS), 1980 (Box 66)
      - Congressional News Notes on innovation and productivity, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
      - Continuing Education for Women, Center for (CEW), 1981 (Box 66)
      - Control Data Corp., 1981-1983 (Box 66)
      - Cost sharing, 1981 (Box 66)
      - C General, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Dearborn Campus, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Dental materials, 1980-1983 (Box 66)
      - Dental Research Institute
        - General, 1981 (Box 66)
        - Policy Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
      - Dentistry, School of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Department of Defense, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Disabled, International Year of, 1982 (Box 66)
      - Distinguished University Professorships, 1983 (Box 66)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (CRED), 1981 (Box 66)
      - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on the, 1979 (Box 66)
      - Economics, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Education, American Council on, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Education, Department of, (Federal), 1981 (Box 66)
      - Education, School of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - EDUCOM (Interuniversity Communications Council, Inc.), 1981 (Box 66)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Energy, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Energy Research Advisory Committee, Office of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Energy Research, Office of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Engineering, College of, 1981; 2 folders (Box 66)
      - English, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - English Language Institute, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Enrollments, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Equipment Needs, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Equipment Research, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Extension services, 1981 (Box 66)
      - E General, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Faculty, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Faculty, New orientation, 1983 (Box 66)
      - Financial Aid, Office of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Flint Campus, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Football Lunches, 1981 (Box 66)
      - F General, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Gene regulation retreat, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Geological Sciences, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Gerontology, Institute of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Governmental Relations, Council on, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Graduate School, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Harrison, Samuel D. (Dr.) Gift to UM, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Hazardous Waste Research Center, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Health and Human Services, Department of, 1982 (Box 66)
      - Health Sciences, Division of, 1981-1982 (Box 66)
      - Higher Education, Center for the Study of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - History, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Honorary Degrees, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Hospital, UM replacement, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Human Genetics, Department of, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Human Growth and Development, Center for, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
      - H General, 1981 (Box 66)
      - Indirect Costs, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Industrial and operations engineering, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Industrial Development Division (IST), 1981 (Box 67)
      - Industry/University Relations, 1978-1981 (Box 67)
      - Industry/University Governor's Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Information Services, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Inquiries and miscellaneous questions, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Institutional Cooperation, Committee on (CIC), 1981 (Box 67)
      - Intellectual Properties Counsel, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Internal Medicine, Department of, 1981 (Box 67)
      - International Fisheries and Aquaculture Development, Consortium for, 1979-1981 (Box 67)
      - Invitations, 1981-1982 (Box 67)
      - Japanese Studies, Center for, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Kelsey Museum, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - KMS Fusion, 1977 (Box 67)
      - K General, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Labor and Industrial relations, Institute of, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Laboratory Animal Medicine, Unit for 1981 Committee on Use and Care of Animals, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Law School, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Library Science, School of, 1979-1981 (Box 67)
      - Lickert, Rensis Lickert Associates, 1980 (Box 67)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 1980 (Box 67)
      - L General, 1981-1982 (Box 67)
      - Market Opinion Research, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Martin Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Mass Spectrometer Needs, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Material and Metallurgical Engineering, Department of, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Mathematics, Department of, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Medical Science Research Building, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Memberships, 1982 (Box 67)
      - Mental Health Research Institute, 1981 (Box 67)
      - MERIT (Michigan Educational Resources and Informational Triad)
        - General, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Board of Directors, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Energy and Resource Research Association (MERRA), 1980 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, 1979-1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Interuniversity Committee on Information Systems (MICIS), 1980 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Research Corp., 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Sea Grant
        - Policy Committee, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Program, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Michigan Society for Medical Research (MISMR), 1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan, State of
        - Governor, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Governor's Committee on High Technology, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Hazardous Waste Management Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
        - Legislature, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Michigan Investment Fund, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Mind Power Conference, 1981 (Box 67)
        - Senate Fiscal Agency, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan State University, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Technology Council, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Technology Fair, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Technology Transfer Consortium, 1982 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Transportation Research Program, 1981-1983 (Box 67)
      - Microbiology, Department of, 1981 (Box 67)
      - Middle English Dictionary, 1981 (Box 68)
      - Midwest Universities Energy Consortium (MUEC), 1980-1981 (Box 68)
      - Molecular genetics, 1981 (Box 68)
      - Music, School of, 1980-1981 (Box 68)
      - M General, 1981 (Box 68)
      - National Academy of Sciences, 1981 (Box 68)
      - National Cancer Institute (Federal), 1982 (Box 68)
      - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (NICHEMS), 1982 (Box 68)
      - National Institute of Health, 1981
        - Budget, 1982 (Box 68)
        - Shared Instrumentation Program, 1981 (Box 68)
      - National Medal of Science, 1979-1981 (Box 68)
      - National Science Board, 1981 (Box 68)
      - National Science Foundation
        - General, 1981 (Box 68)
        - Survey, 1980-1983 (Box 68)
      - Natural Resources, School of, 1979-1981 (Box 68)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Department of, 1981 (Box 68)
      - Near East and North African Studies, Center for, 1981-1983 (Box 68)
      - Neurology, Department of, 1980-1982 (Box 68)